<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LmoWiki</title><subtitle>my personal web notebook</subtitle><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com/atom.xml" rel="self"></link><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com"></link><author><name>undefined</name></author><id>d107b576-e68d-9fe8-09c2-cb3fe6c86e92</id><updated>2021-02-11T10:44:10</updated><entry><title>2021 / 02 / 10</title><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com/#2021%20%2F%2002%20%2F%2010"></link><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com/static/2021%2520%252F%252002%2520%252F%252010.html" rel="alternative" type="text/html"></link><id>cb0dd59b-e578-c802-b8f1-064344f14862</id><updated>2021-02-10T13:10:46</updated><content type="xhtml"><div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Hello world.</p><p>I keep meaning to write more here on a daily basis again. Serial enthusiasm and <a class="tc-tiddlylink tc-tiddlylink-resolves" href="#my%20brain%20is%20a%20pen%20plotter%20drawing%20unoptimized%20paths">my brain is a pen plotter drawing unoptimized paths</a> has me wandering off.</p><p>An irony is that I was starting each of these entries out with &quot;Hello world.&quot; as a way to start with <em>something</em> as an ice breaker - but then I felt bad when the day's entry ended up on the web with solely that text. So then I just re-imposed the stop energy of not writing anything unless I had something to write.</p><p>Also have a notion to rework an RSS feed for these entries - and then a main RSS feed for my lmorchard.com site to wrangle together all the things I might want to &quot;publish&quot; to the world. Maybe I should start an email newsletter. All the cool kids have done it.</p><hr></hr><p>Thinking about censorship &amp; de-platforming lately. I have had a notion for some years that I've been fuzzily turning around in my head. I'm not sure I'm right, and I don't have this all thought out. I have some hunches, though.</p><p>It goes something like this - <a class="tc-tiddlylink tc-tiddlylink-resolves" href="#freedom%20of%20speech%20does%20not%20imply%20a%20right%20to%20amplification">freedom of speech does not imply a right to amplification</a>.</p><hr></hr><p>One of the things I feel like I used to do more was be an information filter &amp; repeater. I'd skim and read items from 100s of RSS feeds and curate what I thought were the good ones into del.icio.us bookmarks with short quippy comments. Sometimes I'd tweet them. Sometimes I'd produce slightly longer blog posts.</p><p>I don't think I do that so much anymore. I think I might like to get back to doing it more. </p><p>Maybe that's what an email newsletter would be for - not that anyone's asking for one from me. They seem kind of insufferable at times.</p><p>Maybe it's just the fashion of the day like belt-onions.</p><hr></hr><p><a class="tc-tiddlylink-external" href="https://hyliu.me/fluent-reader/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Fluent Reader</a>:</p><blockquote><div>Fluent Reader is a local, cross-platform news aggregator with a fresh look. Bring all your favorite sources with you and read distraction-free. </div></blockquote><p>A bare-bones reader app, but with a card view that matches the way I like to view feeds in recent years. Doesn't quite match my flow - I like to skim and open a queue of things to read in browser tabs, rather than read directly in the app. I can do it with this app, but I have to right-click and &quot;open externally&quot; every time. I think I want to poke at this app a bit more.
</p></div></content><author><name>undefined</name></author></entry><entry><title>2021 / 02 / 08</title><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com/#2021%20%2F%2002%20%2F%2008"></link><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com/static/2021%2520%252F%252002%2520%252F%252008.html" rel="alternative" type="text/html"></link><id>f6828476-0545-b7c6-4108-c161330c8c47</id><updated>2021-02-08T12:22:59</updated><content type="xhtml"><div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Hello world.</p><p>From Jim Nielsen’s Blog - <a class="tc-tiddlylink-external" href="https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2021/ikea-and-javascript/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">IKEA, JavaScript, and Assembling Things Yourself</a>:</p><blockquote><div>This is, in a way, the IKEA model: the business (server) gives the customer (client) the materials along with instructions and they serve themselves. Facebook gives each client some instructions—in the form of <a class="tc-tiddlylink tc-tiddlylink-resolves" href="#JavaScript">JavaScript</a> code defining endpoints, templating instructions, etc.—and they assemble the dresser HTML document themselves. </div></blockquote><p>I'd also say an interesting thing here is that you (user) can instruct the client to assemble the furniture in a different way. Leave some shelves out or drill some new holes and move things around. Paint it a different color. Do some <a class="tc-tiddlylink-external" href="https://www.ikeahackers.net/category/hacks" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">IKEA hacks</a> to mix &amp; match parts from different sets in ways not anticipated or condoned.</p><p>Sure, sometimes that means the end result doesn't perform as well or exactly as intended. But, I think these are key features of User Agents on the Web.
</p></div></content><author><name>undefined</name></author></entry><entry><title>2021 / 02 / 04</title><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com/#2021%20%2F%2002%20%2F%2004"></link><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com/static/2021%2520%252F%252002%2520%252F%252004.html" rel="alternative" type="text/html"></link><id>8878a382-c366-2b43-c466-b4de65f1b9aa</id><updated>2021-02-04T12:13:02</updated><content type="xhtml"><div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Hello world.</p><p>Andrew Aquino <a class="tc-tiddlylink-external" href="https://twitter.com/aqandrew/status/1349762018639638528" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tweets</a>: &quot;Those Cistercian numerals from 4 days ago (or maybe 800 years ago) made for some fun React/SVG practice. It's a nifty way to represent integers from 0-9999.&quot;</p><p>This is a neat way to represent numbers. I kind of want to use it as a countdown timer in something.
</p></div></content><author><name>undefined</name></author></entry><entry><title>2021 / 02 / 03</title><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com/#2021%20%2F%2002%20%2F%2003"></link><link href="https://notes.lmorchard.com/static/2021%2520%252F%252002%2520%252F%252003.html" rel="alternative" type="text/html"></link><id>a036092d-5856-e2c3-0403-d3b4784eba2e</id><updated>2021-02-03T09:57:40</updated><content type="xhtml"><div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Hello world.</p><p>I'm writing my morning journal pages, by hand, in ink, with a fountain pen - all of which may come off as precious but I regard as a way to make the whole habit a kind of pleasant meditation thing. Lightly dragging a fountain pen nib to paint ink across nice paper is really gratifying to me.</p><p>This is a small dumb thing, but maybe something I could write more about: Lots of folks complain of hand &amp; wrist pain as why they don't write anything by hand anymore. (Well, that, and computers exist.) The thing to do, though, is learn how to write from the elbow &amp; shoulder rather than flexing fingers &amp; wrist. The larger muscles of the arm are more resilient to sustained effort and can do finer work than for which we often give them credit.</p><p>I've learned to write three pages a day, all by hand, all by using the upper muscles of my arm while keeping my fingers and wrist in a neutral steady position. I have often suffered from wrist pain while typing - probably just shy of carpal tunnel - but I never feel fatigue or pain during or after writing many pages.
</p></div></content><author><name>undefined</name></author></entry></feed>

