<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a13 on Fri, 18 May 2007 00:17:42 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>17.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Thu, 17 May 2007 07:09:56 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Fri, 18 May 2007 00:17:42 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState></expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>135</windowTop>		<windowLeft>420</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>847</windowBottom>		<windowRight>1047</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fourhourworkweek.com.nyud.net:8080/blog/2007/05/16/how-scoble-reads-622-rss-feeds-each-morning/&quot;&gt;How Scoble Reads 622 RSS Feeds Each Morning&lt;/a&gt;.  I like this over-the-shoulder video.  A lot of the reactions I've seen to it &lt;a href=&quot;http://digg.com/tech_news/How_Scoble_Reads_622_RSS_Feeds_Each_Morning&quot;&gt;from digg&lt;/a&gt; and elsewhere are of the &quot;get a life!&quot; or &quot;what a dweeb!&quot; variety.  But, again, this ain't for them.  Some people - like me, with my 500+ feed habit - like to see how other infovores work and like being this connected to information.  Scoble has his Google Reader shared items feed, I've got &lt;a href=&quot;http://del.icio.us/deusx&quot;&gt;my del.icio.us bookmarks&lt;/a&gt; (up to 9012 as of this writing)." created="Fri, 18 May 2007 00:12:11 GMT"/>		<outline text="To read &lt;a href=&quot;http://valleywag.com/tech/yahoo/corporate-branding-gone-awry-261379.php&quot;&gt;this from Valleywag&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://news.com.com/8301-10784_3-9719557-7.html?part=rss&amp;subj=news&amp;tag=2547-1_3-0-20&quot;&gt;this (albeit not as catty) from CNET&lt;/a&gt;, you'd think the mind-control rays would be saturating my cube in a sickly purple/yellow glow from the ceiling mounted wifi access points on a daily basis here at Yahoo!  Fact is, the purple-and-yellow-everywhere thing has been here for quite a long while - it's not amazing and new.  Google's got their thing going on too.  So do a lot of other companies.  The rah-rah mission statement thing, too.  They're really reaching over at Valleywag." created="Thu, 17 May 2007 23:33:16 GMT"/>		<outline text="On the other hand: The mind-control rays must have a retroactive effect, because purple's actually been my favorite color since I was little.  I like the overabundant access to purple sharpies." created="Thu, 17 May 2007 23:39:48 GMT"/>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://simonwillison.net/2007/May/16/libraries/#c36082&quot;&gt;John Resig&lt;/a&gt;:&quot;MochiKit hasn't had a release in over a year and the developers are &lt;a href=&quot;http://groups.google.com/group/mochikit/browse_thread/thread/5b4d434b7a886c4f&quot;&gt;encouraging other users to take control, or use other libraries&lt;/a&gt;.&quot;" created="Thu, 17 May 2007 22:15:54 GMT"/>		<outline text="This bit about &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mochikit.com/&quot;&gt;MochiKit&lt;/a&gt; makes me a tad sad.  Before I got fully &lt;a href=&quot;http://developer.yahoo.com/yui/&quot;&gt;YUI&lt;/a&gt;-ified, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mochikit.com/&quot;&gt;MochiKit&lt;/a&gt; was my favorite &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/blog/2005/12/09/mochis-basic&quot;&gt;Simons Basic cartridge&lt;/a&gt; for the web.  It's not like it went anywhere, and the above-linked discussion thread appears to show that the kit's still in production use, but the folks involved are just too busy actually &lt;i&gt;using&lt;/i&gt; the thing to do releases for the world.  (Which is, of course, largely a thankless task I'd imagine.)" created="Thu, 17 May 2007 22:17:07 GMT"/>		<outline text="Good morning.  I wish that whomever had discovered coffee had been enshrined in myths and legends throughout time, perhaps as some sort of cousin to &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prometheus&quot;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; in some Mediterranean versions of the tale.  I hear it was &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coffee#History&quot;&gt;discovered in Ethiopia&lt;/a&gt; by a goatherd - that seems to have some potential for story." created="Thu, 17 May 2007 07:09:56 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>