<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a13 on Sun, 20 May 2007 02:56:51 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>19.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Sat, 19 May 2007 21:07:02 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Sun, 20 May 2007 02:56:51 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState></expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>120</windowTop>		<windowLeft>417</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>868</windowBottom>		<windowRight>1115</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://nick.typepad.com/blog/2005/10/reading_lists_f.html&quot;&gt;OPML-based reading lists&lt;/a&gt; seem to be a feature that hasn't gotten picked up by any of the major aggregators other than Dave Winer's &lt;a href=&quot;http://opmlwiki.bbcity.co.uk/index.php?title=NewsRiver&quot;&gt;NewsRiver&lt;/a&gt;.  That's kinda sad to me, because I think a meta-subscription to a curated list of feeds is a brilliant idea.  Just doing a one-time import of a reading list isn't good enough - the over-head light bulb comes on when the reading list gets changed on a regular basis by the curator, rotating feeds over time." created="Sun, 20 May 2007 02:51:11 GMT"/>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://alp-uckan.net/free/monitorthis/&quot;&gt;MonitorThis&lt;/a&gt;: &quot;With MonitorThis you can subscribe to 22 different search engine feeds at the same time. Enter a search term and click the 'make monitor.opml' button to get a list of rss feeds in OPML format.&quot;" created="Sun, 20 May 2007 02:49:08 GMT"/>		<outline text="Looks like I need to get back to poking at &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/trac/wiki/FeedMagick&quot;&gt;FeedMagick&lt;/a&gt; and write that OPML reading list powered feed blender module I've been thinking about.  Pass in the URL to an OPML file listing feeds, get one mixed feed back." created="Sun, 20 May 2007 02:49:30 GMT"/>		<outline text="I wonder if it would be interesting and not-too-difficult to have a hook in the OPML Editor to blog and render from the local machine straight to an Amazon S3 bucket?" created="Sat, 19 May 2007 21:26:02 GMT"/>		<outline text="Speaking of &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Go_(board_game)&quot;&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt;, I need to pick that up again as a habit." created="Sat, 19 May 2007 21:15:17 GMT"/>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.starcraft2.com/&quot;&gt;StarCraft II&lt;/a&gt;.  Hot damn.  I've just recently been playing through the original StarCraft, slowly getting my RTS groove back on.  It's been awhile since last I really played any strategy games like that.  They've really gotten the balance perfect in StarCraft.  The game has lasted this long because it's more of an automated board game than a video game, and a friend at work described it as &quot;one great big collection of paper-rock-scissors matches,&quot; where various units trump other units fairly reliably.  Trying to understand it feels a lot like when I started learning to play &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Go_(board_game)&quot;&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt; - but that might just be me." created="Sat, 19 May 2007 21:07:47 GMT"/>		<outline text="Hello world.  Been vaccinated and had blood drawn.  Feel like I've been run over.  I'm kind of a wuss." created="Sat, 19 May 2007 21:07:02 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>