<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a13 on Wed, 23 May 2007 21:05:50 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>23.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Wed, 23 May 2007 14:05:02 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Wed, 23 May 2007 21:05:50 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState></expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>130</windowTop>		<windowLeft>446</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>837</windowBottom>		<windowRight>1024</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="Attended a pre-lunch talk with Jaron Lanier, &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://research.yahoo.com/event/can_networks_be_better_designed_to_suppress_the_worst_qualities_in_human_nature&quot;&gt;Can networks be better designed to suppress the worst qualities in human nature?&lt;/a&gt;&quot;  Interesting meditations on the negative side of mob-formation and blandness in the absence of individuality, Wikipedia-style; offering empathy-evoking avatars in the UI; enforcing a cost to nastyness through persistent, yet possibly still anonymous personas.  Lots more, plenty of shrugs, but an interesting view from a guy I've been reading about since I was a young little netizen." created="Wed, 23 May 2007 19:31:53 GMT"/>		<outline text="A thought for reposting back to &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/&quot;&gt;decafbad.com&lt;/a&gt; from here:  Ignore any top-level outline nodes without children.  But, at midnight each night, gather up and repost the day's outline nodes with children, using the top-level parent as the title.  This is basically how the OPML blog here treats them anyways.  The rational is that something I've bothered to compose into an entry with a title is worth copying over, while anything else is more stream-of-consciousness and tumbleloggy and stays here." created="Wed, 23 May 2007 17:45:28 GMT"/>		<outline text="Hello world." created="Wed, 23 May 2007 14:05:02 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>