<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a13 on Fri, 21 Sep 2007 17:31:28 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>21.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 14:38:11 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 17:31:27 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState></expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>126</windowTop>		<windowLeft>393</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>847</windowBottom>		<windowRight>992</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="Hello world.  Yes, I am a nerd:  I've set up (another) wiki for our household." created="Fri, 21 Sep 2007 14:38:10 GMT"/>		<outline text="Sadness:  I dug the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zeos&quot;&gt;Zeos Pocket PC&lt;/a&gt; out of a box and apparently let out the magic smoke when I tried to plug it into a universal wall wart adapter.  The voltage and polarity were right, and I'd used this adapter with this palmtop before - but this time, it literally smoked and smelled of burning plastic and works no more.  That's kind of an end of an era for me - I'd bought that thing with money I'd won in an Ayn Rand essay contest in High School and used it throughout College to enjoy sitting outside in sunlight with its reflective LCD screen and built-in Microsoft Works to write papers for my psychology classes and stories for my creative writing classes.  Funny what you get sentimental attachments to, albeit however slight." created="Fri, 21 Sep 2007 14:42:09 GMT"/>		<outline text="I see the &lt;a href=&quot;http://support.necam.com/mobilesolutions/hardware/handhelds/MobilePro900/&quot;&gt;NEC MobilePro 900&lt;/a&gt; available for cheap &lt;a href=&quot;http://search.ebay.com/search/search.dll?query=MobilePro+900&amp;MfcISAPICommand=GetResult&amp;ht=1&amp;ebaytag1=ebayreg&amp;srchdesc=n&amp;maxRecordsReturned=300&amp;maxRecordsPerPage=50&amp;SortProperty=MetaEndSort&quot;&gt;on eBay&lt;/a&gt;.  Might one of these be a more modern replacement for my sad old Zeos?  I wonder if it works in the sunshine?" created="Fri, 21 Sep 2007 16:38:39 GMT"/>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mobiletechreview.com/NECMobilePro900.htm&quot;&gt;MobileTechReview&lt;/a&gt;: &quot;The screen is very hard to see outdoors in bright sunlight, so don't buy one of these if you're looking for the ideal beach companion.&quot;  &lt;i&gt;That's a &quot;no&quot;, then.&lt;/i&gt;" created="Fri, 21 Sep 2007 17:29:05 GMT"/>		<outline text="I guess it sounds weird, but I so loved being able to sit outside in fresh air and full-on sunlight with a keyboard-based writing tool that actually was easier to read the brighter the light outside got." created="Fri, 21 Sep 2007 17:29:53 GMT"/>		<outline text="Peeking at the new Amazon Widgets.  Wow - the &lt;a href=&quot;http://wms.assoc-amazon.com/20070822/US/js/8004_6.js&quot;&gt;current JS rendering code&lt;/a&gt; pulled in by the widget bootstrap weighs in at over 77K.  Granted, this shared file should eventually end up in almost everyone's browser and seems to be reused by multiple widgets on a page, but that's hefty for a widget kernel.  Makes me a little more inspired to look into what it would take to make a minimal unobtrusive library for widgets.  jQuery to the rescue, perhaps?" created="Fri, 21 Sep 2007 17:23:27 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>