<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a3 on Mon, 13 Feb 2006 04:49:45 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>12.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Sun, 12 Feb 2006 05:18:38 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Mon, 13 Feb 2006 04:49:44 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState>14</expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>226</windowTop>		<windowLeft>52</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>740</windowBottom>		<windowRight>531</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="I wonder how annoying it would be to pipe my &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/decafbad&quot;&gt;OPML blog's&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://hosting.opml.org/decafbad/blog/rss.xml&quot;&gt;RSS feed&lt;/a&gt; straight into individual asides entries here on this blog, maybe once an hour or three to account for quantum editing flux?" created="Mon, 13 Feb 2006 04:48:31 GMT"/>		<outline text="I keep meaning to do more with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.last.fm/user/deusx/&quot;&gt;my last.fm account&lt;/a&gt;.  I've been dumping my listening habits into it fairly regularly since I got an iPod, and now I've got quite a representative view on my tastes in there.  They've got &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.last.fm/onyoursite/&quot;&gt;some nice blog geegaws&lt;/a&gt;, and here's a nifty feature:  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.last.fm/recommended/wikis/&quot;&gt;Artist wiki page changes filtered by your tastes.&lt;/a&gt;" created="Mon, 13 Feb 2006 04:12:51 GMT"/>		<outline text="A cool use for the &lt;a href=&quot;http://del.icio.us/help/firefox/extension&quot;&gt;del.icio.us extension for Firefox&lt;/a&gt; which just occurred to me:  Since you can bookmark &amp; tag links directly in place on the page with a right-click, without visiting them, I can pluck an MP3 straight &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.msdn.com/alexbarn/archive/2006/02/12/530652.aspx&quot;&gt;from an inline link&lt;/a&gt; and route it to my iPod by way of a podcast subscription to my &lt;a href=&quot;http://del.icio.us/rss/deusx/system:media:audio&quot;&gt;system:media:audio tag&lt;/a&gt; feed.  I'll be listening to &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.msdn.com/alexbarn/archive/2006/02/12/530652.aspx&quot;&gt;this OPML podcast&lt;/a&gt; on the way into work in the morning thanks to this trick." created="Mon, 13 Feb 2006 04:43:06 GMT" type="link" url="http://del.icio.us/help/firefox/extension"/>		<outline text="You know, &lt;a href=&quot;http://scuttle.org&quot;&gt;Scuttle&lt;/a&gt; is a surprisngly full-featured PHP clone of del.icio.us.  I say surprisingly because I first downloaded the latest release version from November, played a bit, and was just a &lt;i&gt;bit&lt;/i&gt; impressed.  Then, I downloaded the CVS version and installed that and got a lot more excited.  I'm considering installing a version of it on my server and mirroring my bookmarks to it.  Still checking out the other clones I've downloaded and installed, though." created="Mon, 13 Feb 2006 04:02:19 GMT"/>		<outline text="Oh yeah, I forgot about &lt;a href=&quot;http://changes.opml.org/&quot;&gt;changes.opml.org&lt;/a&gt;.  I can watch that page and &lt;a href=&quot;http://hosting.opml.org/changes.opml&quot;&gt;associated outline&lt;/a&gt; for updates from people in the OPML neighborhood." created="Mon, 13 Feb 2006 01:00:38 GMT"/>		<outline text="Radio's dead to me, but I've been putting in a lot of time listening to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.radioio.com/radioiorock.php&quot;&gt;radioiorock&lt;/a&gt;.  After awhile, though, the playlist repetitions started to get to me after 4-5 hour stints, so I switched over to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.radioio.com/radioio80s.php&quot;&gt;radioio80s&lt;/a&gt;.  Man, does &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.radioio.com&quot;&gt;radioio&lt;/a&gt; have a single bad station?  Every one I've listened to has some really great selections, B-Sides and &quot;deep cuts&quot; you'd never hear on traditional radio, even back in the day.  Combine this with a living-room resident Xbox equipped with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xboxmediacenter.com/&quot;&gt;Xbox Media Center&lt;/a&gt;, and you're living a few years into the future.  " created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 18:00:37 GMT"/>		<outline text="Speaking of audio, and working on a del.icio.us book, this is a pretty wicked &lt;a href=&quot;http://thepublicservice.com/?p=9&quot;&gt;del.icio.us and Odeo mashup&lt;/a&gt; to facilitate podcast audio comments." created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 21:59:33 GMT"/>		<outline text="I like the sun.  Unlike some geeks who fear the Great Lightbulb in the Big Blue / Grey Room, I thoroughly enjoy a sunny day.  Throughout the grey Michigan winters, I'm generally grumpy.  Today's a sunny day, though.  Unfortunately, the place where I'm most productive on the book at the moment is the basement.  Ah well - at least all the drafts are supposed to be done before Spring has sprung.  I'm going to have to figure out how to be productive yet still enjoy the sun." created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 17:46:42 GMT"/>		<outline text="I've downloaded 6 &lt;a href=&quot;http://del.icio.us&quot;&gt;del.icio.us&lt;/a&gt; clones and installed 4 of them on an iBook so far tonight.  I'm trying to find more.  Interesting features and foibles with each of them. " created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 05:18:37 GMT"/>		<outline text="Oh yeah, another thing about the NewsRiver add-on I've been poking at:  It's got some AJAX XML-RPC code in it that talks to the Aggregator API, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.scripting.com/2006/01/07.html#When:10:37:31PM&quot;&gt;as per Dave's Lazyweb request&lt;/a&gt;.  It's not doing much yet, and I mostly have it hidden, but you can delete stories one-by-one or in groups if you uncomment a few lines of JS." created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 06:36:12 GMT"/>		<outline text="I kind of wish there was a master list of users with blogs on opml.org, just so I could get a sense of who else is in the neighborhood.  Maybe &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com/search?q=site:blogs.opml.org+2006&quot;&gt;this Google search&lt;/a&gt; will help." created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 06:17:37 GMT"/>		<outline text="Also, is it just me, or does the OPML Editor seem like a &quot;pike&quot; reboot?  &quot;;-&gt;&quot;  (This is called, &quot;Fun with the &lt;code&gt;user.html.glossary&lt;/code&gt; Table&quot;)" created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 06:22:15 GMT"/>		<outline text="&quot;the outliner for everyone&quot;" created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 06:23:39 GMT"/>		<outline text="Lightning Fast Blogging with the OPML Editor" created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 06:00:07 GMT">			<outline text="Man, if I thought that Movable Type moved like a barge for me, and WordPress was a  quicker ship, blogging with the OPML Editor is like steering a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pigdog.org/auto/crazy_ivan/link/2420.html&quot;&gt;cavitating torpedo&lt;/a&gt;.  " created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 05:52:48 GMT"/>			<outline text="The mental weight I've placed upon blogging via a web form or even via &lt;a href=&quot;http://ecto.kung-foo.tv/&quot;&gt;ecto&lt;/a&gt; (which is quite a fine program) is such that so many thoughts just evaporate before I bother formally composing them and posting them.  Here, in the OPML Editor, I just tap out a few new outline items and save the outline.  This makes me think of a blog less like Important Capsules of Content and more like a gradually unspooling of brain tangles." created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 05:59:44 GMT"/>			<outline text="And, I don't even need a preview window: The roundtrip on the blog is so fast that you'll probably only barely ever catch me in the middle, and revising is never so ponderous as to think twice before setting the Machine in Motion to Post." created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 06:01:34 GMT"/>			<outline text="Of course, this is the sort of tool Dave Winer uses to edit his blogs, and much ado has been made in the past of his rapid fire revisions.  But, now that I'm playing with this tool again, I can see why he does it:  It's not nefarious, it's just so easy to get thoughts out of your head and splattered onto the web where you can see them and think about them later.  That's kind of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.43folders.com/2004/09/08/getting-started-with-getting-things-done/&quot;&gt;GTD&lt;/a&gt;, I think." created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 06:03:38 GMT"/>			<outline text="I think I can also see how Dave manages to post to so &lt;i&gt;many&lt;/i&gt; blogs, since they're probably all just separate little document windows open for brain threads to unspool into." created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 06:09:01 GMT"/>			<outline text="&quot;brain&quot;" created="Sun, 12 Feb 2006 06:19:59 GMT"/>			</outline>		</body>	</opml>