<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a6 on Thu, 16 Feb 2006 04:50:35 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>15.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Wed, 15 Feb 2006 12:04:18 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 04:50:35 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState></expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>265</windowTop>		<windowLeft>45</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>749</windowBottom>		<windowRight>560</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/dwatts/2006/02/15#When:5:00:28PM&quot;&gt;Donovan points me toward&lt;/a&gt; an &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/spaziopml/2005/08/12#presentingaPresentationTool&quot;&gt;OPML Editor tool&lt;/a&gt; that helps build &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.meyerweb.com/eric/tools/s5/&quot;&gt;S5&lt;/a&gt; presentations from OPML documents, rendered via an XSLT transformation to XOXO that includes all the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.meyerweb.com/eric/tools/s5/&quot;&gt;S5&lt;/a&gt; machinery.  Presentations straight from outlines, with web standards goodness.  Who says you can't have cake and eat it too? " created="Thu, 16 Feb 2006 04:03:17 GMT"/>		<outline text="Later:  Hot damn, it's my &lt;a href=&quot;http://hosting.opml.org/decafbad/l.m.orchard.xml&quot;&gt;Instant Outline as an S5 presentation&lt;/a&gt;.  No, it doesn't make a ton of sense, but it was quick and easy to make this nonsense." created="Thu, 16 Feb 2006 04:21:16 GMT"/>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/dwatts/2006/02/15#When:4:55:09PM&quot;&gt;Donovan's also getting an odd error&lt;/a&gt; from my newsRiver add-on, and the original NewsRiver.  I hope my crud didn't break things, though.  Not sure if this tip helps, but:  You can try running &lt;kbd&gt;viewNewsItems&lt;/kbd&gt; in decafbadNewsRiverSuite directly within the OPML editor to &quot;replay&quot; the last web request and get an in-editor error dialog with a more helpful Go To button to chase the error." created="Thu, 16 Feb 2006 04:07:22 GMT"/>		<outline text="I'm starting to think that the OPML Editor and NewsRiver is a good platform to try throwing together a next iteration of my &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/trac/browser/trunk/hacking_rss_and_atom/ch15_popular_links.py&quot;&gt;popular links script&lt;/a&gt; and some notions I had in mind for &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/trac/wiki/FeedSpool&quot;&gt;FeedSpool&lt;/a&gt;.  I still really like some of the ideas I was exploring with &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/trac/wiki/FeedSpool&quot;&gt;FeedSpool&lt;/a&gt; - but apropos &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/blog/2006/02/13/reading-lists-opml-xoxo-semantic-web-and-tools&quot;&gt;my recent semi-rant about tools&lt;/a&gt;, I should target efforts where more people can take advantage of them more easily.  I love Python, and definitely have a yen for things running on the OS itself - rather than the OS-within-an-OS that is the OPML Editor.  But, I haven't yet had time to bundle my stuff up as a single-icon install like the OPML Editor, and there's a lot of infrastructure already there for the hacking.  So, if you can't beat 'em..." created="Wed, 15 Feb 2006 23:11:54 GMT"/>		<outline text="I'd also like to get back around to adding more things to &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/trac/wiki/FeedMagick&quot;&gt;FeedMagick&lt;/a&gt;, such as maybe some Reading List style features to blend multiple feeds from an OPML list into one output feed.  Need to build some cross-format conversion tools.  I could also see a popular links type script joining &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/2005/12/FeedMagick/&quot;&gt;the suite&lt;/a&gt;.  These sorts of things seem like they could be a server-side complement to the OPML Editor, especially in cases where I can't run Frontier or the OPML Editor on a server yet PHP is available." created="Thu, 16 Feb 2006 03:42:10 GMT"/>		<outline text="Hey &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/yabfog/2006/02/15#When:10:19:13AM&quot;&gt;Dan&lt;/a&gt;, I can't keep up with most of my ideas either - especially with a day like today that had hours of back-to-back meetings.  I've just been &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/decafbad/2006/02/12#lightningFastBloggingWithTheOpmlEditor&quot;&gt;suddenly getting better at spewing things out of my head&lt;/a&gt;.  But I figure if I can get even just a few of them done, I'm in good shape.  Otherwise, I hope someone steals the ideas I don't get around to.  And, yeah, I pretty much do try to stay wired all the time.  &quot;;-&gt;&quot;" created="Wed, 15 Feb 2006 23:07:52 GMT"/>		<outline text="I got an email from Jesse Graffam from over at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.radioio.com/&quot;&gt;radioio&lt;/a&gt;, telling me about &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.radioio.com/radioio90s.php&quot;&gt;their new 90's station&lt;/a&gt;.  I was all like, &quot;Man, a 90's station?  That's starting to make me feel old-- hey, look at all the cool album covers!&quot;" created="Wed, 15 Feb 2006 12:24:14 GMT"/>		<outline text="Ever since I became a &lt;a href=&quot;http://subversion.tigris.org/&quot;&gt;Subversion&lt;/a&gt; convert, my fingers keep hitting &lt;kbd&gt;svn&lt;/kbd&gt; even when I really &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; mean &lt;kbd&gt;cvs&lt;/kbd&gt;.  I had to try three times to get the right command, the last time I checked something out from SourceForge.  And even then, I was rewarded with the usual &quot;update aborted&quot; I get from the overloaded SF CVS servers, but that's another story." created="Wed, 15 Feb 2006 12:04:17 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>