<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a6 on Sat, 18 Feb 2006 02:16:49 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>17.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Fri, 17 Feb 2006 05:03:15 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Sat, 18 Feb 2006 02:16:48 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState></expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>211</windowTop>		<windowLeft>42</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>754</windowBottom>		<windowRight>563</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dontyaknow.com/&quot;&gt;Don't ya know?&lt;/a&gt;  This site &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; needs to be made into a Dashboard Widget.  It seems like a nouveau web version of the email-based &lt;a href=&quot;http://cgi.cs.indiana.edu/~oracle/index.cgi&quot;&gt;Internet Oracle&lt;/a&gt;.  Hmm, I wonder if this site could be rigged up to answer to IMs?" created="Sat, 18 Feb 2006 02:15:12 GMT"/>		<outline text="So, along with my adventures in building the OPML Editor from source, I've also bravely / foolishly tried installing André Radke's &lt;a href=&quot;http://spicynoodles.org/article/20021105&quot;&gt;Sablotron XSLT Extension for Radio / Frontier&lt;/a&gt;.  It was last built in 2002, it appears.  I haven't explored very far yet, but &lt;code&gt;examples.transformTest&lt;/code&gt; worked.  That much really surprised me - I expected an immediate crash.  At any rate, this is one of my long-standing wishlist items for Radio / Frontier / OPML Editor.  Now, I wonder how hard it would be to update the source to build in Xcode..." created="Sat, 18 Feb 2006 01:23:38 GMT"/>		<outline text="If I had the time and learned how to make new extensions for the OPML Editor, it could be madness.  I might even try looping in some RDF code like &lt;a href=&quot;http://librdf.org/&quot;&gt;Redland&lt;/a&gt;.  Madness, I tell you.  It's just a good thing that I don't know what I'm doing." created="Sat, 18 Feb 2006 01:43:32 GMT"/>		<outline text="Just finished listening to Episode #1 of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.silentuniverse.com/&quot;&gt;Silent Universe&lt;/a&gt;.  Holy crap is this a slick and well-produced sci-fi drama podcast.  It's striking me with impressions of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thunderbirdsonline.com/site/&quot;&gt;The Thunderbirds&lt;/a&gt;, Battlestar Galactica, and even Firefly.  Wow.  It's melodramatic without being annoying, has amazing production qualities, and really great voice acting." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 19:40:43 GMT"/>		<outline text="I just got the Knight Rider soundtrack.  Hot.  Had an itch to hear it after listening to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kickassmysticninjas.com/2006/02/15/kamn-show-8-knight-rider/&quot;&gt;KAMN Show #8&lt;/a&gt;.  Now I just have to dig up some viewings of Knight Rider 2000 and Knight Rider 2010." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 16:52:52 GMT"/>		<outline text="Still poking around, but I think I've got an initial stab at an &lt;a href=&quot;http://hosting.opml.org/decafbad/js/main.js&quot;&gt;Unobtrusive JS solution for Haloscan comments&lt;/a&gt; on this here blog, using &lt;a href=&quot;http://mochikit.com&quot;&gt;using MochiKit&lt;/a&gt;.  Bugs abound.  Once it seems to be stable, I may do a little write up about it.  In the meantime, feel free to steal my code.  It's written &lt;i&gt;almost&lt;/i&gt; to the point of being self-orienting and a simple drop-in add-on to Haloscan and OPML Editor blogs.  There's one configuration URL in there that I want to factor out." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 18:08:09 GMT"/>		<outline text="I've mentioned our office's &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/blog/2005/10/21/the-bluetooth-ghost&quot;&gt;Bluetoothed Ghost&lt;/a&gt; before, now I mention him again.  He is still here, still unleashing prodigious streams of urine at the bathroom stalls whilst emitting the occasional semi-voluntary grunts and still conducting quite vocal business via a Bluetooth headset.  Flushes and the sounds of other restroom visitors abound.  How can the people with whom he does business not realize he's doing his business at the same time?  And then, how can he bring himself to shake anyone's hand when he just zips up and strides out of the lavatory with nary a handwash.  This man is easily in his 50's.  I expect he's not new to the world and the customs of our country - he speaks English without accent, which I can hear clearly while I'm quietly occupying my own stall.  At any rate, this disturbs me.  And now, I hope, it has disturbed you and perhaps amused you.  And, if you are a creature such as this man...  &lt;b&gt;STOP IT.&lt;/b&gt;" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 19:57:15 GMT"/>		<outline text="Reading &lt;a href=&quot;http://dannyayers.com/archives/2006/02/15/treehandedness/&quot;&gt;Danny's bit about Treehandedness&lt;/a&gt; reminds me that I've been meaning to mention something about outline UI for awhile now.  And that something is this:  Why are the disclosure triangles on the left, yet the scroll bar is on the right?  I think it's left-to-right reading and the visual semantics of a bullet point colliding with the general right-handedness of most GUIs.  If you're a lefty, you may have a different take on this.  But at any rate, if you take a peek at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.decafbad.com/blog_attachments/miniagg-1.jpg&quot;&gt;my latest in aggregator UI design&lt;/a&gt;, such as it is, you'll see that I've opted for sticking the triangles on &lt;i&gt;both&lt;/i&gt; sides and clustered the per-item controls over by the scroll bar on the right.  You shouldn't need to bounce your mouse from side to side on the screen to interact with this stuff." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 15:29:58 GMT"/>		<outline text="Crap.  I do believe my laptop's senescence is well underway.  There were already two weird smudgey light bits on the display, but now there's a decidedly black colon shaped &lt;i&gt;hole&lt;/i&gt; in the screen now.  I can even look close and pan my head back and forth and see a little actual &lt;i&gt;parallax&lt;/i&gt; between the pixels displayed and this hole." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 15:03:49 GMT"/>		<outline text="Three guys are having lunch" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:04:24 GMT">			<outline text="&lt;i&gt;This is a really rough draft of a scene that popped into my head this morning...  No offense intended to any Opie's, Randolf's, or Xavier's out there - and all apologies in case I've misrepresented your respective lunchtime positions.  Laugh, it's funny.&lt;/i&gt;" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:58:58 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Opie&lt;/b&gt; (entering): Hey, guys!  How's it going!?  Have I got some stories to tell you!" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:05:40 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Randolf&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;http://copia.ogbuji.net/blog/2005-06-27/Wow___XML_&quot;&gt;Jesus, that's an ugly shirt!  And how'd you learn to walk that way?&lt;/a&gt;" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:06:18 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Xavier&lt;/b&gt;: Your shirt isn't much better, Randolph.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://microformats.org/about/&quot;&gt;At least mine's made from natural fibers.&lt;/a&gt;" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:06:58 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Opie&lt;/b&gt;: Eh, my shirt's fine.  It was free, it fits, and it was in the closet when I got up." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:08:07 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Randolf&lt;/b&gt;: And did you have to come in that gas-guzzling smogmobile of yours? &lt;a href=&quot;http://dannyayers.com/archives/2006/02/10/feedlists-in-rdf/&quot;&gt;I wish you'd driven an electric car.&lt;/a&gt;" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:10:28 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Xavier&lt;/b&gt;: ...or maybe &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/blog/2005/11/27/i-wish-it-were-in-xoxo&quot;&gt;a bicycle cleverly constructed from coconuts!&lt;/a&gt;  It's biodegradable and partially digestible!" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:12:02 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Opie&lt;/b&gt;: Er, um, okay.  My car's pretty cool!  &lt;a href=&quot;http://support.opml.org/download&quot;&gt;It was free, it runs, and it came with a steering wheel and automatic transmission!&lt;/a&gt;  It could do with a wheel cover and a seat belt, though." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:12:36 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Randolf&lt;/b&gt;:  &lt;a href=&quot;http://copia.ogbuji.net/blog/2005-07-06/OPML__XOXO&quot; title=&quot;I use emacs plus the command line for most of my coding, and after trying out a half dozen blog posting tool for posting to Copia, I ended up writing an e-mail-to-post gateway so that I can enter text (markdown) into a UI I'm already familiar with, Evolution's e-mail composition window.&quot;&gt;When I drive, I prefer a stick shift and a system of ropes and pullies to steer.&lt;/a&gt;" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:13:46 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Xavier&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;http://microformats.org/wiki/faqs-for-rdf&quot;&gt;I like a conveyance that helps make me one with the nature of the world.&lt;/a&gt;" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:14:21 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Opie&lt;/b&gt;: That all sounds like a pain in the ass.  How'd you guys get here?" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:16:19 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Randolf&lt;/b&gt;:  I walked - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dajobe.org/2004/01/turtle/&quot;&gt;I've got comfortable shoes&lt;/a&gt;.  I do &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.w3.org/2001/11/IsaViz/&quot;&gt;have a fun scooter&lt;/a&gt; in the garage, though." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:30:40 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Xavier&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;http://wordpress.org/&quot;&gt;I took the bus&lt;/a&gt;, though sometimes I walk.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.decafbad.com/blog/2005/07/12/xoxo_outliner_experiment&quot;&gt;I'm seriously working on that coconut bicycle, though.&lt;/a&gt;" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:32:46 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Opie&lt;/b&gt;: Yikes!  How do you guys get much done during the day?" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:30:56 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Randolf&lt;/b&gt;: Oh, I get by.  I get up really early and start writing, having woken from dreams of electric &lt;i&gt;flying&lt;/i&gt; cars I'll have in the future." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:47:21 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Xavier&lt;/b&gt;: I blog and write search engines.  That keeps me plenty busy." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:50:03 GMT"/>			<outline text="&lt;b&gt;Opie&lt;/b&gt;: Ugh.  So, anyway.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/blog/2006/02/16/just-put-on-your-xoxo-colored-glasses&quot;&gt;I'll shop for a hybrid or something this week&lt;/a&gt;, but I'm not giving up my car.  Now, do you guys want to hear my stories, or what?" created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:47:43 GMT"/>			</outline>		<outline text="I think I'm some kind of nerd mutant at times.  I mean, on one hand I've got a lot of respect for a well-considered and specified data format and I have a great deal of appreciation for elegance.  On the other hand, I've gotten a lot of experience with and have had a lot of twisted fun in munging and scraping from one embodiment of information into another." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 04:48:08 GMT"/>		<outline text="My recent revival of interest in the OPML Editor has struck me a bit like &lt;a href=&quot;http://psylux.psych.tu-dresden.de/i1/kaw/diverses%20Material/www.illusionworks.com/html/figure_ground.html&quot;&gt;a figure/ground reversal&lt;/a&gt; - you know, the candlestick/faces thing?  After having stared at the data format for so long, ducking into this editor and finding utility flipped my bit.  It's the tools that get my work done, not the data.  But then, I think one of my mutant nerd powers is to stare at one of those figure/ground situations until I can make the thing strobe in my head and become something else entirely.  It's what I did with Perl versus Python, and later with emacs versus vi.  I guess this is the next thing." created="Fri, 17 Feb 2006 04:52:23 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>