<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a6 on Mon, 20 Feb 2006 05:04:24 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>19.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Sun, 19 Feb 2006 06:17:51 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 05:04:24 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState></expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>302</windowTop>		<windowLeft>43</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>760</windowBottom>		<windowRight>483</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="Scoping out &lt;a href=&quot;http://ma.gnolia.com&quot;&gt;Ma.gnolia&lt;/a&gt; a bit today, and I've noticed a few &lt;a href=&quot;http://ma.gnolia.com/people/IraGlass&quot;&gt;rather&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://ma.gnolia.com/people/AltonBrown&quot;&gt;famous&lt;/a&gt; - and decidedly &lt;a href=&quot;http://ma.gnolia.com/people/TedAllen&quot;&gt;non-tech geek&lt;/a&gt; - people have accounts there.  This has me scratching my head a bit:  Are these people friends of the site owners?  Spontaneous fans of this site's brand of social bookmarking?  Paid shills?  Seeing these sorts of faces showing up at an up-till-now all-alpha-geek party seems a bit suspect to me.  It also seems rather non-&lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/blog/2006/02/09/a-long-tailed-creative-yawp&quot;&gt;long-tailed&lt;/a&gt; and celeb-attached to me.  But then, I'm weird and it could be all on the up and up." created="Mon, 20 Feb 2006 01:28:28 GMT"/>		<outline text="More writing today, interspersed with bits of procrastination.  I started roughing out &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/trac/wiki/OpmlServer&quot;&gt;a standalone OPML Community Server in PHP&lt;/a&gt; this afternoon.  Who knows how far I'll get, but it has initial bare-bones support for registration, login, and upstreaming.  And when I say &quot;support&quot;, I don't mean anything grandiose - it's really just a bunch of XML-RPC methods at this point, but it could turn into something interesting." created="Sun, 19 Feb 2006 05:43:15 GMT"/>		<outline text="There &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; one thing that kind of threw me for a loop in the OPML Editor user interface, though:  The &quot;Change Community...&quot; menu item assumes a port of 5337 for any XML-RPC server that's not &lt;code&gt;support.opml.org&lt;/code&gt;.  That made me have to manually tweak my &lt;code&gt;dotOpmlData.prefs&lt;/code&gt; to talk to my own server on port 80." created="Sun, 19 Feb 2006 06:03:32 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>