<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a6 on Sun, 26 Feb 2006 17:41:31 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>25.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 05:20:46 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Sun, 26 Feb 2006 17:41:31 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState>4</expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>190</windowTop>		<windowLeft>45</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>751</windowBottom>		<windowRight>538</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="Hey Donovan, could you by chance send me that &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/dwatts/2006/02/24#myNewOpmlCoffeeMug&quot;&gt;new coffee icon set&lt;/a&gt; you found?  I, um... Well, you see, I like coffee.  A lot.  And I signed up &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.iconbuffet.com/delivery&quot;&gt;over at IconBuffet&lt;/a&gt;, but it says I need to have it sent to me from a friend.  Mmm... coffee." created="Sun, 26 Feb 2006 03:05:21 GMT"/>		<outline text="Heh, and I almost forgot about this image (courtesy of my old pal &lt;a href=&quot;http://stingthebee.nu/wp/&quot;&gt;Jim Renaud&lt;/a&gt;):&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;img src=&quot;http://decafbad.com/2004/06/les.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;" created="Sun, 26 Feb 2006 03:14:21 GMT"/>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.scripting.com/2006/02/25.html#When:3:34:02PM&quot;&gt;From Dave&lt;/a&gt;: &quot;&lt;i&gt;I'm glad people are thinking about how long the free hosting is going to last, because, while I have no plans to stop hosting sites for free, it will eventually happen, and when it does, it's better if people are prepared.&lt;/i&gt;&quot;  Exactly &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/decafbad/2006/02/18#freeHostingCommunityBootstrapAndChangingDiapers&quot;&gt;my sentiment&lt;/a&gt;.  It's best to consider the free hosting as great for bootstrap, but be ready to leave the nest at some point." created="Sun, 26 Feb 2006 02:30:51 GMT"/>		<outline text="Browser as mini-OPML-Editor via AJAX" created="Sat, 25 Feb 2006 18:53:55 GMT">			<outline text="An idea that occurred to me last night as I dozed off (no, my brain never stops):  In-browser editing of OPML blogs and outlines for when you're &quot;on the road&quot;. " created="Sat, 25 Feb 2006 18:42:39 GMT"/>			<outline text="Playing with AJAX-style XML-RPC for &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/decafbad/2006/02/22#When:11:34:01AM&quot;&gt;my NewsRiver add-on&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;decafbad.com/trac/wiki/OpmlServer&quot;&gt;knowing that the OPML Community Server has an XML-RPC API for posting OPML data&lt;/a&gt; - I've got a notion that it just &lt;i&gt;might&lt;/i&gt; be possible to make your web browser into a &quot;mini-OPML Editor&quot;. " created="Sat, 25 Feb 2006 18:54:20 GMT"/>			<outline text="I'd revive my &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com/blog/2005/07/12/xoxo-outliner-experiment&quot;&gt;XOXO Outliner&lt;/a&gt;, join it up with an XOXO-to-OPML conversion in JavaScript and an AJAX call to the OPML Community Server, and save the results to the server all from the browser.  Of course, I'm not sure how you'd then get the OPML back from the server onto your home-base OPML Editor, since I think the transfer is more of an upstream than a two-way sync...  but, just getting this hare-brained idea out there." created="Sat, 25 Feb 2006 18:54:29 GMT"/>			</outline>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.opml.org/amyloo/2006/02/25#imgSrchttphostingopmlorgamylooositeimages1dotohgif&quot;&gt;Amyloo's mockup of an OPML Editor 1.0 site&lt;/a&gt; is looking pretty nerdily neat.  The grid paper style has me thinking of Moleskine-esque connotations." created="Sat, 25 Feb 2006 18:40:10 GMT"/>		<outline text="I think this sporadic habit of mad blogging here, with occasional selections copied over to &lt;a href=&quot;http://decafbad.com&quot;&gt;0xDECAFBAD&lt;/a&gt;, seems to work pretty well.  At any rate, it's time for sleep." created="Sat, 25 Feb 2006 05:20:46 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>