<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a10 on Fri, 11 Aug 2006 16:41:50 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>10.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Thu, 10 Aug 2006 14:00:26 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Fri, 11 Aug 2006 16:41:49 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState></expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>306</windowTop>		<windowLeft>46</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>869</windowBottom>		<windowRight>505</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="Here's a gripe:  Why does iTunes seem to peg the CPU when downloading Podcasts?  On every machine I've run it, iTunes seems to hog all available cycles when running through my subscriptions.  What's so hard about checking podcasts?  Even when there are no new downloads, the processor load is enormous.  I've &lt;i&gt;written&lt;/i&gt; podcast tuners.  It's not that intensive." created="Thu, 10 Aug 2006 16:49:19 GMT"/>		<outline text="Man, now &lt;a href=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/uk_news/4778615.stm&quot;&gt;this news from the UK&lt;/a&gt; makes me not want to take a plane anywhere.  And it's not because I'm afraid someone would blow up the plane - it's because I'd have to spend hours upon hours alternating between stark boredom and the fear that some child would start screaming bloody murder for 3 hours straight and I'd have no headphones with which to escape.  This happened on the flight from Detroit to San Francisco, but &lt;i&gt;with&lt;/i&gt; headphones on hand, thank goodness.  It's hard being crammed into small spaces with strangers.  This sounds whiny, but what's more of a danger?  A hypothetical bomb, or someone snapping from the stress?  Maybe it'll turn out that this plot to blow up planes ends up proving to have been a very close call, but these sorts of measures are themselves really starting to sound like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/2006/08/07/only_traitors_try_to.html&quot;&gt;the works of traitors&lt;/a&gt;." created="Thu, 10 Aug 2006 14:01:46 GMT"/>		<outline text="Hello world.  Good morning.  Mmm, coffee." created="Thu, 10 Aug 2006 14:00:26 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>