<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><!-- OPML generated by OPML Editor v10.1a13 on Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:23:40 GMT -->
<opml version="1.1">	<head>		<title>07.opml</title>		<dateCreated>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 19:35:00 GMT</dateCreated>		<dateModified>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:23:40 GMT</dateModified>		<ownerName>l.m.orchard</ownerName>		<ownerEmail>l.m.orchard@pobox.com</ownerEmail>		<expansionState></expansionState>		<vertScrollState>1</vertScrollState>		<windowTop>50</windowTop>		<windowLeft>397</windowLeft>		<windowBottom>837</windowBottom>		<windowRight>1048</windowRight>		</head>	<body>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://code.google.com/p/iui/&quot;&gt;iui - &quot;Provide a more &quot;iPhone-like&quot; experience to Web apps (on or off the iPhone)&quot;&lt;/a&gt;" created="Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:21:48 GMT"/>		<outline text="Now...  why didn't Apple release something &lt;a href=&quot;http://code.google.com/p/iui/&quot;&gt;like that&lt;/a&gt;?  Given how concerned they are about the integrity of the thing, I would hope maybe they'd want to help developers achieve some consistency in the UI of their apps to help maintain the quality." created="Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:22:19 GMT"/>		<outline text="Nothing concrete, but:  Still thinking about an open, self-hosted, federated app inspired by Twitter, Jaiku, Pownce.  Thinking about &lt;a href=&quot;http://cr.yp.to/im2000.html&quot;&gt;Internet Mail 2000&lt;/a&gt;.  Thinking about friends, friends of friends, private mutually-negotiated inboxes.  Thinking about &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ietf.org/html.charters/atompub-charter.html&quot;&gt;Atom Publishing Protocol&lt;/a&gt; instead of SMTP and Atom feeds of messages.  Thinking about groups and &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shibboleth&quot;&gt;shibboleths&lt;/a&gt;.  Thinking about the new &lt;a href=&quot;http://framework.zend.com/&quot;&gt;Zend Framework&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://gophp5.org/&quot;&gt;going PHP 5&lt;/a&gt;.  Thinking about some open conventions to make it all work for any web app." created="Sat, 07 Jul 2007 20:32:04 GMT"/>		<outline text="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gearlive.com/news/article/q307-how-to-use-irc-on-the-iphone/&quot;&gt;How To: Use IRC On The iPhone With Colloquy.&lt;/a&gt;  Since Colloquy's already got Safari / WebKit built-in as its display engine on OS X, and the software generates displays using XSL, HTML, CSS, and JS - it's a snap to decouple the elements of the display across a web connection.  Tired: X11, Wired: HTTP" created="Sat, 07 Jul 2007 19:36:09 GMT"/>		<outline text="Hello world.  It's 07.07.07.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://jchutchins.net/&quot;&gt;The End is Nigh!&lt;/a&gt;" created="Sat, 07 Jul 2007 19:35:00 GMT"/>		</body>	</opml>